Kartik Galewar

Technology Analyst.

Passionate in Information Technology services and interested in learning new technologies. Love challenges which is essential in one's growth and progress.

Worked as a MERN stack developer and on front-end technologies for different projects in Infosys Limited and Sycamore Software Solution..

Nanded,Maharashtra. **8010034889 kgalewar@gmail.com**

EXPERIENCE

Infosys Limited, Pune — *Technology Analyst*

MARCH 2020 - PRESENT

Website Development:

Worked as a Core Front end as well as Backend developer which involved extracting business data from database and processing it in front-end along with some additional business functionalities in ReactJs.Developed entire sites for a Food processing company with complex business requirements in

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, ReactJs.

Also Working as a technical advisor to client regarding the functionality and performance of their sites and acting as a bridge between client and Technology leads.

Sycamore Software Solutions Pvt. Ltd., Pune — Software Engineer

MAY 2017 - MARCH 2020

Website Development:

Developed several websites. The projects consist of Hollywood movies website and web application designed using JavaScript, HTML 5, CSS3, JQuey, XML & JSON.

World Wide Release Date(WWRD):

Build the 50+ WWRD pages Responsive site with CSS, HTML with Table and Inline CSS.

Newsletters:

Build the 150+ Newsletters using HTML with Table and Inline CSS.

Localization of websites:

Localization of websites in different languages such as Latin America, German, French, Spanish, Italian, Thai, Brazil, Chinese, Japanese, Korean, etc. We provide Localisation as a service to our client Warner Brothers and Paramount, where we translate those websites into respective languages.

EDUCATION

Marathwada Institute of Technology(MIT) Aurangabad - BE (Computer Science and Engineering), Aurangabad JUNE 2012 - JUNE 2016

SKILLS

ReactJs,Redux, Javascript,Jquery, Html5, Css3

TOOLS

Github,BitBucket,
Postman,Thunder
Client,
File Zilla.

DATABASE

MongoDB (Beginner).NodeJs (Beginner)